https://www.drjsalomon.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
PROCEDURES:
Brazilian Butt Lift
MED SPA:
LASER TREATMENTS
NEW Thermi SmoothLaser Tattoo RemovalScar RemovalLaser Resurfacing (Fraxel, Fractional CO2)Thermage CPTIplGentle YagLaser Hair Removal (Gentle Lase)
BOTOX AND FILLERS
Botox CosmeticRadiesseRestylanePerlaneJuvederm
BODY TREAMENTS
NEW EmSculpt®NEW ThermiVaNEW Thermi RFNEW ThermiTightNEW Velashape IIICavitationBody ThermageSclerotherapyMassage MenuSpa PackagesNutrition and WellnessMyers Cocktail
SKIN CARE
Facial TreatmentsDiamondtome MicroSkinceuticals DermaplaningHydrafacial
OTHER
TestimonialsEventsCharityFormsPrivacy NoticeBLOGSpanish Version
IN OFFICE PRIVACY NOTICE
Please read our in office Notice of Privacy Practices. To download right click on the link below and save.In Office Privacy NoticeThe file is in PDF, to download Adobe Acrobat Reader please use the following link.
ON LINE PRIVACY NOTICE
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site or fill out and submit a form.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To personalize your experience:Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs
To improve customer service:We continually strive to improve our website based on the information and feedback we receive from you.
To process requests and transactions (feedback, request for information, newsletters, etc):Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for express purpose of delivering the purchased products, information, or service requested by you.
To send periodic emails:The email address you provide for either processing an order, or for requesting information on our services, may be used to send you additional new information and updates pertaining to your order or our services offered, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. Note: You can notify us at anytime when you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, by using our contact page.
To administer promotions, surveys, and site features.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of industry standard security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information provided.
Do we use cookies?
We do use cookies.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety, however, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Third Party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
Online versus Offline (in office) Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our websites and not to information collected offline. Please refer to our In Office Privacy Notice.Please Click Link:In Office Privacy Notice
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. This policy was last modified on 10/28/2010.
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below:
www.drjsalomon.com6705 Red Road Suite 708Coral Gables,FL 33143
— Leave your feedback —
